[{
        "question": "What is the name of the mummy that the Doctor encountered on the Orient Express?",
        "choice1": "The Foretold",
        "choice2": "The Gorgon",
        "choice3": "Tutankhamun",
        "choice4": "Hatshepsut",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What planet do the Daleks originate from?",
        "choice1": "Telos",
        "choice2": "Earth",
        "choice3": "Skaro",
        "choice4": "Clom",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What alien race is erased from your memory when you stop looking at them?",
        "choice1": "The Family of Blood",
        "choice2": "The Silence",
        "choice3": "The Daleks",
        "choice4": "The Sontarans",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What species is the Doctor's friend Madame Vastra?",
        "choice1": "Sea Devil",
        "choice2": "Cyberman",
        "choice3": "Silurian",
        "choice4": "Saturnyn",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the frightening stone angelic creatures known as?",
        "choice1": "Cupids",
        "choice2": "Weeping Angels",
        "choice3": "Hosts",
        "choice4": "Saviours",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the approximate lifespan of the family of blood?",
        "choice1": "3 days",
        "choice2": "3 weeks",
        "choice3": "3 months",
        "choice4": "3 years",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Dalek experimented on its own cells to introduce human elements?",
        "choice1": "Dalek Thay",
        "choice2": "Dalek Sec",
        "choice3": "Dalek Omega",
        "choice4": "Dalek Caan",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What Earth creatures do the Judoon resemble?",
        "choice1": "Rhinoceros",
        "choice2": "Cats",
        "choice3": "Wasps",
        "choice4": "Wolf",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these aliens have NOT had at least one emotion removed?",
        "choice1": "Cyberman",
        "choice2": "Dalek",
        "choice3": "Modified Ood",
        "choice4": "Jagrafess",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the creator of the Daleks?",
        "choice1": "Davros",
        "choice2": "Kaled",
        "choice3": "Voord",
        "choice4": "Strax",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What species was introduced in 1975 and re-appeared in the show's 50th anniversary special?",
        "choice1": "Slitheen",
        "choice2": "Jagrafess",
        "choice3": "Ood",
        "choice4": "Zygons",
        "answer": 3
    }
]